So for those who don't know, Smart Funny in Black is on May 18th in Los Angeles and we are doing a free ticket drive.
Now the way this is going to work is we have people donating and when y'all donate into our smartfunnyinblack.com account, we are able to put that money towards up to 140 free tickets.
So far, we have secured 67, yes, but we need the rest, all right, because we want to get all 140 free tickets filled up so we can get all 140 people to come to the show who may not have the money to go to the show, but maybe just need to be at the show because it's a good time.
So if you can't make the show or you want to support Smart Funny in Black but you don't live in LA, here's a way to do it and not only support the show, but support your community.
You can go to smartfunnyinblack.com, donate any amount of money, and that is going to be a part of the pool that is going to pay for 140 free tickets for folks to come to see the show.
See y'all there. Thank you so much.
I forgot to add, when it comes to the free tickets drive for Smart Funny in Black, consider that one ticket costs $45.
So, you know, that's basically the cost of one ticket.
Also, we are closing down the drive in two days on May 10th.
So we're trying to get these last tickets as much as possible to the people.
So, if you are down, then donate.
Smart Funny in Black dot com.